Ogunnaike Princess Ayomide

Software Engineer

Frontend developer

08076824974

Payomide53@gmail..com

 \times

Lagos - Nigeria



About Me

Highly skilled and experienced Frontend Developer with a passion for creating visually appealing and user-friendly web applications with Strong understanding of responsive design and cross-browser compatibility. Strong desire to stay current with the latest technologies and trends in the field.

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS TailwindCss
 Bootstrap
 Styled-Components
- JavaScript Jquery React Rest APIs
 Jest
- Git/Github

Work Experience

Oct - Sept 2022 - 2022

Hngi9 Internship

Finished the program as one of the top 100 Frontend developer, with over 700 frontend developers that started the program

- Developed user interface with modern JavaScript frameworks, Html5, CSS3
- Built a Metaverse Website containing all kinds of houses in it and made sure it was responsive on all screens.
- Learned new skills and applied daily tasks to improve efficiency and productivity
- Collaborated with team members and Product Managers to achieve target results by making a Reputational Management Website that's responsible for taking down bad reviews.
- Proved successful working within tight deadlines and fast-paced atmosphere.
- Developed and maintained courteous and effective working relationships.
- Experience in working with APIs and back-end technologies.
- Proven ability to work collaboratively with cross-functional teams, including designers and back-end developers.
- Strong problem-solving and critical thinking skills.

Oct - Sept

Primatech Innovation

2021 - 2021

- Created basic Landing page websites using just HTML and CSS.
- Worked closely with developers on creating-new code.
- Prioritized and problem solved several tasks concurrently with minimum supervision.
- Developed team communications and information for meetings.

Education

2014-2017

ODUDUWA UNIVERSITY, IPETUMODUN

4 years

Osun state - Ife

obtained a B.S.C in Biochemistry